woof
呜
don't play in the driver's seat
不要玩司机的座位
parking here you'll get a ticket
在这里停车,你会有车票的
hey stop hey
在这里停车,你会得到一张车票 嘿,嘿,停下,嘿,嘿,嘿
嘿,停,停,停,嗨
hey stop hey
little bear you shouldn't stick things
嘿,停下,嘿,嘿,小熊小熊 你不应该粘东西的东西
小熊,你不该粘东西
little bear you shouldn't stick things
like this on cars
小熊,你不该把这种东西 挂在汽车上
在汽车上像这样
like this on cars
oh
像这样在汽车上啊哦
哦
oh
oh sorry it's dangerous to be outside by
哦,哦,对不起,这是危险的 外面,
哦,对不起,这是危险的 外面,
oh sorry it's dangerous to be outside by
yourself come on we'll take you home
哦,对不起,你一个人在外面很危险 过来,我们送你回家
go police car
警车
stop you shouldn't sit in the driver's
停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停停
seat it's very dangerous okay
停下,你不该坐在司机座位上 很危险,好吗?
not in the passenger seat either
也未在客座中
foreign
外国或外国或外国在客座中未在客座中
Little Bear you should never stick your
小熊,你不该坚持
head or arms out of the window that was
"小熊小熊" 你永远不应该把你的头或胳膊 伸出窗外
或手从窗外的 头或手臂
head or arms out of the window that was
really close
头或手从窗口外的 真正紧紧的窗口
I I got it
我来拿,我拿
here
我在这里拿到的
two burgers please all right
两包汉堡,谢谢,两包汉堡包
here you go wow thanks
在这里,你去那里 哇,谢谢
hi hello
在这里,你走了哇,谢谢你好 你好,你好你好,你好 你好,你好,你好,你好,你好,你好你好,你好,你好,你好,你好你好,你好你好,你好你好你好,你好你好,你好你好你好,你好你好,你好你好你好,你好你好你好你好,你好你好你好,你好你好你好,你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好你好
Sheriff Labrador why is my son with you
拉布拉多警长 为什么我儿子和你在一起
Mr bear it's dangerous for little bear
拉布拉多警长 为什么我儿子跟你在一起 熊先生 对小熊很危险
熊先生,对小熊来说危险
Mr bear it's dangerous for little bear
to play outside alone please be careful
熊先生 小熊一个人在外面玩很危险 请小心
独自在外外玩,请小心
to play outside alone please be careful
sorry I was so busy today I didn't keep
独自在外面玩,请小心小心 对不起,我今天很忙 今天我没有保持
对不起,我今天忙得没来
sorry I was so busy today I didn't keep
an eye on him oh thank you for bringing
抱歉我今天忙得那么忙 对不起,我没看好他 哦,谢谢你带过来
看着他 哦 谢谢你带给我
an eye on him oh thank you for bringing
him back please try these my special
谢谢你们把他带回来 请尝尝我的特餐
请尝尝我的特餐
him back please try these my special
Burgers they're really good wow such big
请尝尝我特制的汉堡 超好吃的 哇这么大
汉堡真是好吃,哇好大呀
Burgers they're really good wow such big
burgers I know we're all right please
汉堡很好,哇哇 这么大的汉堡,我知道我们没事,谢谢
и笵и⊿ㄆ癠
burgers I know we're all right please
have some
汉堡包,我知道我们没事,请吃一点
有一些
have some
uh
来来来来来 来来来来来来
hey
嘿
whoa let's go hey
哇,我们走吧,嘿,嘿
oh what's going on
哦,这是怎么回事
all right
没事
oh no he's done right now
哦,不,他已经做了现在
Little Bear
小熊小熊
hey yes
小熊小熊 嘿,是的
get in the car
上车
Pio Sheriff Labrador a burger truck is
皮奥警长拉布拉多 汉堡卡车是
out of control and little bears in it we
皮奥警长拉布拉多 拉布拉多 一辆汉堡卡车失控 里面还有小熊
无法控制,小熊在其中,我们
out of control and little bears in it we
need your help
失去控制,小熊在里面 我们需要你的帮助
需要您的帮助
need your help
foreign
外籍人士需要您的帮助
have you follow the truck
你跟着卡车走
hey hold on Ty
跟着卡车走 抓好泰泰
喂,等一下,泰泰
hey hold on Ty
get us on top of the truck no problem
等阿泰扶我们到卡车顶上,没问题
把我们放在卡车上,没问题
get us on top of the truck no problem
leave it to me
把我们放在卡车上,没问题,交给我
sorry my mistake
对不起,对不起,对不起,对不起
fasten your seat belts hold tight I'm
系好安全带 紧紧系紧紧安全带
gonna break
系紧安全带 紧紧系紧安全带 我要打破安全带
huh
中、英、法、俄、西
oh no the break's broken yeah
哦,没有休息的打破了耶
yeah
耶 耶,耶
Papio where can I make an emergency stop
是的,帕皮奥,我在哪里可以做 紧急停留
帕皮奥,我在哪里可以紧急停车?
Papio where can I make an emergency stop
there's an emergency laying ahead
前方有紧急情况
got it
前面有紧急紧急事件
yeah too many cars ahead leave it to me
是啊,前面的车太多 留给我吧
sit up straight
是啊,前面的车太多 留给我坐直了,坐直了
oh phew
呼呼呼呼呼呼
that was so scary I'll never play in the
那样吓人,我永远也不会在
driver's seat again
那样吓人,我再也不坐在驾驶座上玩了
Sheriff labrador's safety talk
拉布拉多警长的安全谈话
kids when you ride in a car always sit
小孩坐车的时候 小孩坐车坐着坐着坐着
in the back and fasten your seatbelts
小孩坐车的时候 小孩坐车的时候 总是坐在后面 系好安全带
在后面系上安全带,系上安全带,
in the back and fasten your seatbelts
never stick your heads or arms out of
系上安全带 永远不要把头或胳膊伸出来
永远不要把你的头或胳膊伸出来
never stick your heads or arms out of
the window or play in the driver's seat
永远不要把头或手伸出窗外或坐在驾驶员座位上玩耍
窗口或播放司机座位
the window or play in the driver's seat
if you start the guard by mistake you
如果您错误启动警卫, 请在窗口中键入窗口, 或者在驾驶员座位中玩游戏 。
如果你误开卫兵,你就会
if you start the guard by mistake you
can cause a serious traffic accident
错误启动保安时,您可引发严重的交通事故。
造成严重交通事故
can cause a serious traffic accident
hurting yourself and others let's stay
造成严重交通事故 伤害自己和其他人 让我们留下来吧
伤害自己和他人 让我们留下来吧
hurting yourself and others let's stay
safe when we're outside and when we ride
当我们在外面和骑马时,让我们保持安全
当我们在外面,当我们骑马时,安全安全
safe when we're outside and when we ride
in a car
当我们在外面,当我们骑上车时,当我们安全时,当我们在外面,当我们乘坐汽车时,当我们安全时,当我们安全
坐在车里
in a car
dangerous overloaded car
一辆危险超载车
kids look Daddy's got a new car
孩子们看爸爸有辆新车
oh
孩子们看爸爸有辆新车哦
well done Daddy we want to go for a
做得好爸爸,我们想去
drive in the new car all right sign up
爸爸,做得好,爸爸,我们想在新车 开车去兜兜兜风
在新车的驱动器中 所有权利注册 所有权利注册
drive in the new car all right sign up
everyone
在新车的驾驶中 所有权利注册 每个人
每个人,每 人, 每 人, 每 人, 每 人, 每 人, 每 人
everyone
let's just stay home today please we
我们今天就呆在家里吧,拜托了
really want to go
我们今天就呆在家里吧,拜托了,我们真的要走了
真的想离开
really want to go
man we'll just drive around for a bit
男人真的想走,我们开车兜兜风
男人,我们只是开车 绕过一圈
man we'll just drive around for a bit
okay okay said tight let's go
男人,我们只是开车 绕一圈好 好,说紧,我们走吧
okay
还好
yeah no what's that smile
不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不,不
watch me
看着我
wow it's so clean
哇 这么干净
it's dirty again hey you should drive
又脏了,你应该开车
safe with manners
又脏又脏了 哎,你应该带着礼仪开车安全
保险箱中,有安全处所,有安全处所,
safe with manners
looks like something's wrong with that
看起来有点不对劲
car don't be let's follow it
那辆车好像出问题了 别跟着我们走
车不要被我们跟着它走
car don't be let's follow it
papion ready for backup got it
车不要跟着它走 准备备好后援 拿到了
thank you
感谢您,感谢您
there were too many people in the car
车里的人太多了
that's so dangerous we need to stop the
车里有太多人 如此危险,我们必须阻止他们
这太危险了 我们需要阻止
that's so dangerous we need to stop the
car
那太危险了,我们得停车
why am I on the main road
为什么我在主要道路上
oh no watch out
为什么我在主要道路上? 哦,不小心
I can't control the car oh
我控制不了车,哦
Watch Out
监视观察出
Mr wild Goose's car is out of control we
野鹅先生的车失控了
need your help
野鹅先生的车失控 我们需要你的帮助
需要您的帮助
need your help
move aside move aside
移动 移动 移动 移动 移动 移动
oh that was close it was so scary
哦,是近在眼前,它是如此可怕
we're going downhill I need to stop the
我们要下山了,我必须阻止
car
我们下山了,我要停车
汽车
car
ah the brakes not working
啊 刹车没用啊
why is there smoke coming out
为什么有烟冒出来
Mr World Goose stop the car the Red's
世界鹅先生 拦住红色的车
not working
世界鹅先生阻止红色的车失灵
right
右右右右右
now
现在
here
在这里
hey huh
嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿
哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈
hey huh
Sheriff Labrador there's a cliff up
拉布拉多警长 拉布拉多有悬崖
拉布拉多警长 拉布拉多警长 悬崖悬悬
Sheriff Labrador there's a cliff up
ahead what we need to stop the car right
拉布拉多警长 拉布拉多警长 拉布拉多警长 拉布拉多警长 前面有个悬崖
前面需要的车停在前面 车停在前面
ahead what we need to stop the car right
now
前面我们需要的车停在前面 立刻停车
it's a cliff
这是一个悬崖
everyone's safe
人人安全,人人安全
thank you so much for saving us Mr Wild
非常感谢您救了我们 维尔德先生
Goose you broke the traffic rules you're
谢谢你救了我们 野鹅先生 你违反了交通规则
鹅,你违反交通规则
Goose you broke the traffic rules you're
coming with us to the police station
鹅,你违反交通规则 跟我们去警察局
和我们一起去警察局
coming with us to the police station
I'll never overload my car again
和我们一起去警察局 我再也不超载我的车了
Sheriff Labradors safety talk
拉布拉多警长安全谈话
kids it's very dangerous to ride in a
孩子们,骑在
car that has more people than it was
孩子们骑车非常危险 车里的人比以前多
汽车上的人比以前多
car that has more people than it was
designed to seat when riding in a car
汽车上人比汽车上座椅设计的人多
设计成坐坐座时乘坐汽车
designed to seat when riding in a car
kids should sit in safety seats in the
儿童应坐在安全座椅上。
孩子们应该坐在安全座位上
kids should sit in safety seats in the
back and fasten their seat belts and
孩子们应该坐在后面的安全座椅上 系好安全带
系好安全带和系好安全带,
back and fasten their seat belts and
while riding you should remain seated
你应当坐好,坐好,坐好,坐好,坐好,坐好,坐好,坐好,
你们坐着坐着坐着坐着吧!
while riding you should remain seated
and keep your heads and arms inside the
骑马的时候,你们应当坐着,坐着坐着,坐着坐着,坐着坐着坐着,坐着坐着坐着,坐着坐着坐着坐着,坐着坐着坐着坐着,坐着坐着坐着坐着,坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着,坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着,坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐坐着,坐着坐着坐着坐着坐坐着,坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着,坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着,坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着,坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着,坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着,坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着,坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着,坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着,坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着,坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐着坐坐坐着坐着坐坐坐坐着坐坐着坐坐着坐着坐着
并保持你们的头和手在
and keep your heads and arms inside the
car
保持你的头和手臂 在车内
汽车
car
please remember that
汽车请记住
don't copy dangerous Acts
不复制危险行为
super
不要复制危险动作超级
超级
super
Superman
超超超超
超人
Superman
hey
超人 嘿
嘿
hey
what are you doing Dolby I'm stupid
嘿,你在干嘛? 多比,我笨
you shouldn't copy dangerous scenes from
你不应该复制危险场景
TV like that you could get hurt okay
你不应该像在电视上那样 复制危险场景 那样受伤
hi I'm Sheriff Labrador
你好 我是拉布拉多警长
I need your help
你好 我是拉布拉多警长 我需要你的帮助
what Yobe let's go
尤比,我们走吧
hey
嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿
it's no use changing like super Kate man
和超级凯特男人一样改变是没用的
brother chick why did you do such a
弟弟小鸡,为什么你这样做
dangerous thing
弟弟小妞,你为什么做这么危险的事?
危险危险物品
dangerous thing
I
危险物品I
一一
I
I was trying to be like a super cute man
我想像个超可爱的男人
it's very dangerous you mustn't do that
我想做一个超可爱的超可爱的男人... ...这是非常危险的,你不能这样做
这是非常危险的 你不能那样做
it's very dangerous you mustn't do that
okay
这是非常危险的,你不能这样做,好吗?
um
毫米
there's a fire in the forest kids are
森林里着火了 孩子们
stuck there oh no it might be the little
森林里着着着火了 孩子们被困在那里
不,不,它可能是一个小
stuck there oh no it might be the little
hamsters papion come take us got it
哦,不,它可能 可能是小仓鼠猪 来带我们得到了它
Sheriff Labrador I found the kids
拉布拉多警长 我找到孩子们了
location
拉布拉多警长 我找到了孩子的位置
位置位置位置
location
let's land now
方位位置,我们降落吧
上岸吧,我们上岸吧
let's land now
got it
让我们的土地,现在得到它
the fire is too strong
火太烈了
find a place where there is less fire
找一个火灾较少的地方
Dobby and I will go down there
找到一个火少的地方 多比,我会去那里
your fireproof cloak and follow me hey
你的防火斗篷 跟着我,嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿
hey yeah
你的防火斗篷,跟我来 嘿嘿嘿嘿嘿耶
嘿耶
hey yeah
this way
嘿,是的,这边走
以此方式
this way
oh
哦
what should we do
我们应当做些什么
oh
哦
Sheriff Labradors let's get out of here
拉布拉多警长,我们走吧
watch out this way
注意看这边
we need your help
注意这边,我们需要你的帮助
the fire spreading so fast
火焰迅速蔓延,
hurry under the clothes
火势迅速蔓延 衣服下急急急急忙的
衣服下快点,衣服下快点
hurry under the clothes
I'm coming
穿上衣服快点,我马上来
where is Batman
蝙蝠侠在哪里
hold on tight
紧紧抓住
we'll never call me dangerous ass again
我们再也不会叫我危险屁股了
Sheriff Labrador safety talk
拉布拉多警长安全谈话
kids you shouldn't copy dangerous scenes
拉布拉多治安官 安全谈话儿童 你不应该模仿危险场景
孩子不应该复制危险场景
kids you shouldn't copy dangerous scenes
from TV only people who have trained a
孩子们,你不应该从电视上 复制危险场景 只有受过训练的人
仅受过电视培训的人
from TV only people who have trained a
lot and no special stunts can do them
只有那些受过很多训练,没有特殊特技的人才能做
并且没有特殊特技
lot and no special stunts can do them
so they're not for us to do if you try
也没有特别特技特技可以做 所以如果你尝试
所以,如果你尝试,他们不是我们做,如果你做
so they're not for us to do if you try
to copy them you could hurt yourself or
所以如果你试着复制的话 我们就不能这么做 你可能会伤到自己 或者
复制它们,你会伤害自己或伤害自己
to copy them you could hurt yourself or
Worse please remember that
拷贝它们,你会伤害自己 或者更糟 请记住
更糟糕的是,请记住
Worse please remember that
what
更糟糕的是,请记住
什么什么是
what
phone call from a stranger
陌生人打来电话
sweetie I'm going to the market don't
陌生人打来电话,我要去市场
亲爱的,我要去市场,不要
sweetie I'm going to the market don't
open the door to anyone and don't answer
甜心,我要去市场,不要向任何人开门,不要回答
向任何人敞开大门,不要回答
open the door to anyone and don't answer
the phone if you don't know the number
向任何人敞开大门,不接电话 如果你不知道号码
如果你不知道电话号码 电话号码
the phone if you don't know the number
bye
如果你不知道电话号码的话 电话就挂了
拜拜
bye
I who's calling
我是谁的呼唤
huh I don't know this number I shouldn't
我打给谁 我不知道这个号码 我不应该
我不知道这个号码 我不该
huh I don't know this number I shouldn't
answer it
我不知道这个号码 我不应该回答的
回答它
answer it
what if it's an emergency
如果是紧急事件,请回答
hello this is little sheep huh it's a
哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈
kid hello little sheep are your parents
哈哈哈哈哈哈哈,一个小孩 哈哈哈哈哈 哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈 哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈 小羊是你父母
你好 小绵羊是你的父母
kid hello little sheep are your parents
home
你好 小绵羊 你父母在家吗?
家 家
home
they went out
回家后,他们都出门了
他们出门了
they went out
they're not at home that's great who is
他们出门了,他们不在家,这是伟大的谁是
他们不在家,这是伟大的谁是
they're not at home that's great who is
this I'm Uncle Bear a friend of your mom
他们家不在家,这很好,谁是谁? 我是熊伯伯伯伯伯,你妈妈的朋友
我是你母亲的朋友 熊叔叔
this I'm Uncle Bear a friend of your mom
and dad don't you remember me uh Uncle
我是熊叔叔,你父母的朋友 你不记得我了吗? 叔叔
爸爸不记得我了 叔叔
and dad don't you remember me uh Uncle
Bear that's right I bought a cake for
爸爸你不记得我 熊叔叔了 没错,我买了蛋糕
熊,没错,我买了一个蛋糕
Bear that's right I bought a cake for
you
熊,对了,我给你买了个蛋糕
您 您 的 您 您
you
can you wait outside I'll be there soon
你可以在外面等我一下 我马上就到
你到外面等,我马上到
can you wait outside I'll be there soon
okay I'm coming
你可以在外面等,我马上到 好,我马上来
好,我来了
okay I'm coming
Uncle Bear
好,我来了,大熊叔叔
熊叔叔
Uncle Bear
there you are come with me
大伯伯伯,你跟我走
oh sweetie where are you
亲爱的,你在哪里?
hi I'm Sheriff Labrador
你好 我是拉布拉多警长
what we'll be right there
我们即将到来的东西
my daughter was playing with Clay right
我女儿和Clay玩弄我
here but she disappeared when I got back
我女儿和Clay一起玩,我回来时她失踪了
我回来的时候她失踪了
here but she disappeared when I got back
don't worry leave it to us
我回来后她就失踪了 放心交给我们吧
放心吧,交给我们吧
don't worry leave it to us
the windows are locked from the inside
放心吧,就交给我们吧 窗户从里面锁着
窗口从内部锁定
the windows are locked from the inside
and the room looks all right you
窗窗从里面锁着 房间看起来还不错
房间看起来还不错
and the room looks all right you
oh oh there's Clay on the phone looks
房间看起来还不错,你好吗 哦,有克雷 在电话的外表
哦,有Clay在电话外表
oh oh there's Clay on the phone looks
like little sheep answered the phone
哦,有克莱在电话 看起来像小绵羊接听电话
就像小绵羊接听电话一样
like little sheep answered the phone
papiam check this number got it
就像小绵羊回答 电话papiim检查这个号码得到它。
Papiam 检查这个号码 得到它
papiam check this number got it
oh no it's a fraud call maybe little
哦,不,这是个欺诈电话 可能有点小
sheep was tricked by the phone call
哦,不,这是个欺诈电话 也许小羊被电话骗了
被电话骗骗的绵羊
sheep was tricked by the phone call
where's the location of this number
被电话骗骗的羊 是这个号码的位置
right here rainbow apartment let's go
彩虹公寓就在这里 走吧
hi where is the bad person hiding
躲藏的坏人在哪里?
ouch hello your pizza is arriving soon
你披萨马上就到 躲着打招呼的坏人在哪里?
你好啊,你的披萨披萨快到了
ouch hello your pizza is arriving soon
pizza delivery I have a good idea
你好啊,你的披萨披萨快到 送披萨了,我有个好主意
送比萨饼,我有个好主意
pizza delivery I have a good idea
so hungry
送比萨饼,我有个好点子 肚子好饿
肚子饿肚子饿饿的
so hungry
what is it congratulations you've won a
饥饿,饥饿 是什么,它是它的 恭喜你赢得
恭喜你赢得了
what is it congratulations you've won a
free Pizza coupon a free pizza
恭喜你赢得了免费比萨饼优惠券 免费比萨饼
oh this is your last chance if you don't
哦,这是你最后的机会 如果你不这样做
want it this delicious pizza will go to
哦,这是你最后的机会 如果你不想要的话,如果你不想要它 这个美味的比萨饼会去
想要这个美味的比萨饼
want it this delicious pizza will go to
the next lucky person
想要这个美味的比萨饼 送给下一个幸运的人
下一个幸运的人
the next lucky person
wow
下一个幸运的人哇哇
right here and pizza delivery it's here
就在这里 送披萨和送披萨
oh my pizza
哦,我的比萨饼
it's my pizza oh it's mine that's off
是我的比萨饼哦,这是我的,关闭了
it's fine
这是我的比萨饼 哦,这是我的,它关闭 它的罚款
police I gotta run
警察,我得走了
hey
警察,我得走了,我得走了,嘿嘿
嘿
hey
look stop
观看停止
what's that
这是什么
stop right there
站在那里别动
goby
食人动物
use super capture I
使用超级抓取 I
super catcher
超级超级捕捉者
what
超级超级捕猎者什么
go
上去
you haven't eaten your pizza yet
你还没吃披萨呢
oh
哦
nobody can run away from me little sheep
没有人能逃离我的小绵羊
you're safe now we got the bad guy
没有人能逃开我的小绵羊 你安全了 现在我们抓到坏人了
our calls from strangers again
我们又从陌生人那里打来电话
Sheriff labrador's safety talk
拉布拉多警长的安全谈话
kids if you get a phone call from a
如果你接到来自A.A.A.A.A.A.A.A.A.A.A.A.A.A.A.A.A.A.A.A.A.A.A.A.A.A.A.A.A.A.A.A.A.A.A.A.A.A.A.A.A.A.A.A.A.
stranger don't answer it just tell your
如果你接到陌生人的电话 孩子们就别接 直接告诉你
陌生人不要回答 只要告诉你
stranger don't answer it just tell your
parents if you happen to answer a call
陌生人不要回答 只要告诉你父母 如果你碰巧接了电话
如果您恰巧接听了电话,请通知父母:
parents if you happen to answer a call
from a stranger never tell them you're
如果你碰巧接陌生人的电话 父母从不告诉他们你是
从陌生人那里从不告诉他们你是
from a stranger never tell them you're
alone and don't say anything about you
陌生人从陌生人那里从不告诉他们你一个人 也不要说你什么
自己一个人 什么都不要说
alone and don't say anything about you
or bad people might trick you please
不要说你或坏人会骗你
或坏人可能会骗你
or bad people might trick you please
remember that
或坏人可能会骗你 请记住
记住
remember that
monster on the street
街上的怪物
but the Rainbow Theater will start soon
但彩虹剧院将很快开始
okay but always safely first
但彩虹剧场很快就要开演了 好,但总是安全第一
可以,但必须首先安全
okay but always safely first
hi I'm Sheriff Labrador Sheriff Labrador
你好 我是拉布拉多警长 拉布拉多警长
I saw a monster on the road it was so
我是拉布拉多警长 拉布拉多警长 我看见一个怪物在路上
我看到一个怪物在路上,它是如此
I saw a monster on the road it was so
scary a monster we'll be right there
我看到一个怪物在路上... ...路上,它是如此可怕... ...一个怪物,我们马上就到
一个可怕的怪物 我们马上就到
scary a monster we'll be right there
yeah
耶 耶,耶
oh where are they
哦,他们在哪里
huh
哦,他们在哪里啊哈哈哈
中、英、法、俄、西
huh
Sheriff's Labrador a monster showed up
警长的拉布拉多拉布拉多 一个怪物出现了
on the road all of a sudden and I had a
警长的拉布拉多拉布拉多 一个怪物突然出现在路上 我有一个
突然在路上 突然间,我有一个
on the road all of a sudden and I had a
car crash because of it
突然在路上 突然间我撞了车
造成汽车撞车事故
car crash because of it
it was so scary
因为车撞车太吓人了
there's no such thing as a monster
没有怪物这样的怪物
but we saw it please find the monster
没有怪物这样的怪物 但我们看到了它 请找到怪物
但我们看到它了 请找到怪物
but we saw it please find the monster
don't worry
但我们看到它了 请找到怪物不要担心
别担心
don't worry
there's no case that I can't saw
别担心,没有我看不到的案子
没有我看不见的病例
there's no case that I can't saw
oh
哦
I found some Footprints huh
我找到了一些脚印啊
they came from the other side of the
他们从火狱的另一侧来,
guardrail over there
他们从那边的护栏的另一侧来,
在那边的护栏上,
guardrail over there
the person that caused the car crash
造成车祸的人
must have jumped over the guardrails to
造成车祸的人 一定是从护栏跳到
一定是从护栏上跳下去的
must have jumped over the guardrails to
cross the road
一定是跳过护栏才过马路的
跨过公路
cross the road
do you remember what the Monster looked
你还记得怪兽的表情吗?
你还记得怪物的样子吗?
do you remember what the Monster looked
like
你还记得怪物长什么样吗?
its hair was like a bird a bird's nest
它的头发就像鸟鸟 鸟巢
its nose was red and its mouth was very
它的头发就像鸟鸟鸟的巢 鼻子红红 嘴唇非常
鼻子红红,嘴巴红
its nose was red and its mouth was very
big
鼻子红红,嘴巴大
like this
像这样
exactly that's how it looked the monster
就像这样,它看起来就像怪物一样
怪兽就是这么看的
exactly that's how it looked the monster
looks so scary
怪兽看起来如此可怕
看上去好吓人啊
looks so scary
I don't think it's a monster it looks
看上去好恐怖,我并不认为它是一个怪物 它看起来像一个怪物
我不认为它看起来像一个怪物
I don't think it's a monster it looks
like the clown from The Rainbow Theater
我不认为是怪物 看起来像彩虹剧院的小丑
就像彩虹剧院的小丑一样
like the clown from The Rainbow Theater
now they will be a clown show at the
就像《彩虹剧院》里的小丑 现在他们将成为《彩虹剧院》的小丑表演
现在,他们将是一个小丑表演 在
now they will be a clown show at the
Rainbow Theater tonight we were on our
他们将成为今晚在彩虹剧院的 小丑表演
彩虹剧院今晚 我们一起
Rainbow Theater tonight we were on our
way there Toby let's go
今晚彩虹剧院 我们正要去的路上 托比 我们走
look over there the monster is the Clown
看那边 怪物是小丑
my goodness you're late you need to be
我的上帝,你迟到了 你需要
on stage right away don't worry I took a
天啊,你迟到了,你需要马上上台 不要担心,我拿了
立刻上台,别担心,我拿了
on stage right away don't worry I took a
shortcut I never late
不要担心我走捷径,从不迟到
快捷快捷快捷键我从未迟到
shortcut I never late
gorilla oh you broke the traffic rules
捷径我从不迟到大猩猩哦 你违反了交通规则
大猩猩哦,你违反交通规则
gorilla oh you broke the traffic rules
you're under arrest oh no
哦大猩猩哦,你打破了交通规则 你被捕了哦不
你被捕了哦 不对
you're under arrest oh no
stop right there
你被捕了哦,别停在那儿
is this a new show
这是新秀
s
这是新显示 s
okay okay
还好,还好
get him
抓住他
don't go over the guard rail
不要越过警卫的铁轨
later
后来
that was so scary gorilla you broke the
被你打碎的大猩猩 被你打碎了
traffic rules you're coming with us to
你打破了交通规则 你和我们一起去
交通规则 你跟我们一起去
traffic rules you're coming with us to
the police station I'll never go over
交通规则,你要跟我们去警察局 我绝不会过去
警察局,我永远不会过去
the police station I'll never go over
the guardrails again as a shortcut
派出所,我再也不会走捷径 越过守卫的铁栏
Sheriff labrador's safety top
拉布拉多警长的安全顶层
kids we need to follow the traffic rules
孩子们,我们需要遵守交通规则
always use sidewalks wherever you go and
孩子们,我们需要遵守交通规则 总是使用人行道 无论你去哪里
无论你走到哪里 总是用人行道
always use sidewalks wherever you go and
don't go over guard rails as a shortcut
人行道总是用人行道 不论你走到哪里 都用人行道作为捷径
不要绕过护栏作为捷径
don't go over guard rails as a shortcut
if you do you might get in a car
不要把守铁栏作为捷径 可能坐上车
如果你愿意的话,你可能会坐上一辆车
if you do you might get in a car
accident and your life might be in
如果你有的话,你可能会遭遇车祸 你的生命可能会在
和你的人生可能发生意外
accident and your life might be in
danger as well remember what we've
并且你的生命可能面临危险 记住我们所遭遇的
也记住我们所知道的
danger as well remember what we've
learned today
记住今天我们学到的东西
今天学到的今天
learned today
don't play in the parking lot
不要在停车场玩
oh no it's my turn
哦,不,轮到我了
you'd better find a good place to hide
哦,不,轮到我了,你最好找个好地方躲起来
huh
中、英、法、俄、西
little chick little chick where are you
小鸡小鸡小鸡小鸡 你在哪里
little chick
小鸡小鸡小鸡小鸡小鸡在哪里 小鸡小鸡在哪里
小鸡小妞
little chick
good
良好
Hey kid what are you doing here it's
小子,你在这里干什么?
dangerous in the parking lot
小子,你在这里干什么? 停车场很危险
what you were playing hide and seek in
你们所隐匿的,和你们所寻求的,
the parking lot that's really dangerous
你在停车场里玩的玩捉迷藏的游戏 真的很危险
那停车场非常危险
the parking lot that's really dangerous
please help me find my little brother
那停车场非常危险 请帮我找到我弟弟
请帮我找到我的小弟弟
please help me find my little brother
don't worry there's no case that I can't
帮我找到我弟弟,别担心 没有我办不到的案子
不要担心,没有案子我不能办
don't worry there's no case that I can't
solve
别担心,我办不到案子
Hey kid were you playing hide and seek
小子,你在玩捉迷藏
on this floor uh-huh we need to search
嘿,小子,你玩捉迷藏 寻找在这个地板 嗯,我们需要搜索
我们需要在地板上搜索
on this floor uh-huh we need to search
every corner of this floor copy that
我们需要搜查这层楼的每个角落
每一个角落的地板复制件
every corner of this floor copy that
little Jake little Jake
每个角落的地板 复制这个小杰克小杰克小杰克
huh
中、英、法、俄、西
little jig oh
哦,小小鸡鸡哦
these are my little brother's jelly
这是我弟弟的果冻
beans
这是我弟弟的果豆
little chick might be around here
小妞可能就在这附近
somewhere then we might find him by
小妞可能就在这附近... ...然后我们就可以找到他了
然后我们可能会在某处发现他
somewhere then we might find him by
following these jelly beans
跟着这些果冻豆子 我们就能找到他
the jelly beans have stopped here that
果豆停止在这里,
means
果豆停止在这里 这意味着
中指
means
little chick might have taken the
意思是小鸡可能已经采取
小鸡可能已经采取了
little chick might have taken the
elevator huh it's dangerous around here
小妞可能坐电梯 这儿很危险
这附近很危险的电梯
elevator huh it's dangerous around here
we need to find him as soon as possible
这里很危险 我们得尽快找到他
我们需要尽快找到他
we need to find him as soon as possible
oh
我们需要尽快找到他哦
哦
oh
the second floor
二楼二楼
excuse me have you seen a little chick
对不起,你见过一个小妞吗?
This Tall no I haven't
对不起,你有没有见过一个小妞 这个高个子,我还没有
Toby found anything no
托比发现没有
oh my little brother brother where are
托比没有找到什么
哦,我的小弟弟 我的小弟弟在哪里
oh my little brother brother where are
you oh
哦,我的小弟弟,你在哪里,哦
it's little chick
是小小鸡鸡
follow me
跟我来
little chick
小鸡小妞
watch out
当心
nice little chick
漂亮的小小妞
watch out
当心
foreign
外国
labrador's safety dock
拉布拉多的安全码头
kids never play in a parking lot you
小孩子从来不在停车场玩
might be in a car's blind spot as you're
孩子从来不玩 在一个停车场 你可能会在汽车的盲点 汽车的盲点,因为你是一个
可能是在汽车的盲点 汽车的盲点,因为你
might be in a car's blind spot as you're
not tall enough to be seen by the driver
可能是在汽车的盲点 因为你不够高 无法被司机看到
身高不够高,司机看不到
not tall enough to be seen by the driver
and with so many intersections in a
不够高,无法被驾驶员看到 车内有这么多十字路口
并有如此多的十字路口
and with so many intersections in a
parking lot drivers can't always react
车司机不能总是反应
停车场司机不能总是反应
parking lot drivers can't always react
immediately and accidents Could Happen
停车场司机不能总是立即反应 事故可能发生
立即发生事故和可能发生事故
immediately and accidents Could Happen
also beware of idle cars as you could
立即发生事故 可能发生事故 也尽可能小心闲置车辆
也尽量小心闲置的汽车。
also beware of idle cars as you could
easily get hurt if they start to move
也注意闲置的汽车,因为如果汽车开始移动,很容易受伤。
当他们开始移动时很容易受伤
easily get hurt if they start to move
remember to stay alert when you're in a
当他们开始移动时 很容易受伤 当他们开始移动时 记得保持警惕
记得记得当你身在
remember to stay alert when you're in a
parking lot and don't play around always
记得记得在停车场时保持警惕 不要总是到处玩
停车停车场,别总是到处玩
parking lot and don't play around always
Safety First
停车停车场,不要总是玩游戏 安全第一
don't play in construction sites
建筑工地不玩
up right there
在上面的顶上
don't even think about it
就在上面 别想都别想
you will never catch me
你永远抓不到我
yeah we did it
是啊,我们做到了
I'll never steal a hand you're going to
是啊,我们做到了,我永远不会偷 一只手,你要去
我不会偷你一手的手
I'll never steal a hand you're going to
the police station with me
我从不偷手 你跟我一起去警察局
always has heavy wow there are so many
总是很重,哇,有这么多
construction vehicles in here let's go
这儿有这么多的建筑车辆,我们走吧
这里的建筑车辆,我们走吧
construction vehicles in here let's go
in
这里的建筑车辆,我们进去吧
内
in
oh no little wild geese went into the
哦,没有小野鹅进入
construction site it's dangerous in
哦,没有小野鹅进入建筑工地 这是危险的
建筑工地很危险
construction site it's dangerous in
there we need to get them out
建筑工地很危险 我们得把他们弄出来
wow it's a loader it's my favorite
哇,这是装货机,是我最喜欢的
watch out
当心
construction sites are very dangerous
建筑工地很危险
you should never play here okay okay
建筑工地很危险,你不该在这里玩,好吗?
你不应该在这里玩,好吗?
you should never play here okay okay
we need to find him right now
我们需要马上找到他
wow
哇哇哇哇
it's so dirty
哇,好脏呀,好脏呀
oh
哦
no oh it hurts
不,哦,它伤害
what's going on
发生什么事了
where are you
你在哪里,你在哪里
watch out
当心
it's so dangerous here and it will be
这里很危险,会很危险
hard to find him
这里很危险,很难找到他
很难找到他
hard to find him
we need to use search equipment got it
很难找到他 我们需要使用搜索设备
the awesome searching robot little
令人惊叹的搜索机器人小
wonton he'll help us find what we're
他会帮助我们找到我们
他会帮我们找到我们的本性
wonton he'll help us find what we're
looking for
他会帮助我们找到我们要找的东西
寻找
looking for
sorry he's not perfect just yet
很遗憾他现在还不是完美
hey
嘿
I am a little ducks
我是个小鸭子
hold on
等一等
popcorn where did you find this
爆米花 你在哪里找到这个的
little wonton lead the way now
爆米花 你在哪里找到这个小温顿现在领路的
小温顿现在领路了
little wonton lead the way now
oh
小温顿领路了哦
oh I'm so dizzy
哦,我好头晕啊
foreign
外国
's calling for help
呼救的呼救
over there
在那里呼救的呼救
he's in danger hurry let's go okay
他有危险,快点,我们走吧,没事的
laughs
笑笑
we're all right thanks little wonton
我们没事,谢谢小圆圆
Gary will never play in construction
我们没事,谢谢小温顿盖瑞 永远不会在建筑中玩
加里永远不会在建筑中玩
Gary will never play in construction
sites again
加里再也不会在建筑工地玩了
Sheriff Labradors safety talk
拉布拉多警长安全谈话
construction sites are very dangerous
拉布拉多警长安全谈话 建筑工地非常危险
建筑工地很危险
construction sites are very dangerous
they are full of Steels and cement
建筑工地非常危险 充满钢铁和水泥
他们有钢铁和水泥,
they are full of Steels and cement
construction vehicles often move around
里面都是钢铁 水泥建筑车辆经常到处走来走去
建筑车辆经常到处走来走去
construction vehicles often move around
you might get hit and even get hurt
建筑车辆经常在你周围移动 你可能会被击中 甚至受伤
你可能会被击中 甚至受伤
you might get hit and even get hurt
cranes lift materials up in the air they
你可能会被击中 甚至受伤的起重机 升起材料 在空气中,他们
起重机在空气中提升材料
cranes lift materials up in the air they
might fall and hurt people
起重机在空气中提升材料 可能会坠落并伤害人
可能摔倒伤人
might fall and hurt people
there are also big and deep holes if you
可能摔倒和伤害人... ...那里也有巨大和深洞... ...如果你...
也有大洞和深洞 如果你
there are also big and deep holes if you
get close to one you might fall in kids
如果你接近一个你可能会掉进孩子的洞 里面还有大洞和深洞 如果你接近一个你可能会掉进孩子的洞
接近一个你可能会掉落的孩子
get close to one you might fall in kids
please remember these and never play in
请记住这些 永远不要玩
construction sites
请记住这些,不要在建筑工地玩
建筑工地
construction sites
the dangerous manhole cover
危险的井眼覆盖
危险的坑孔覆盖
the dangerous manhole cover
s
危险的坑孔覆盖S
little rabbit little rabbit where are
小兔子小兔子 小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子
you
小兔子小兔子小兔子 小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子小兔子
ow
owowow
ow it hurts
痛啊痛啊痛啊
woof hi I'm Sheriff Labrador
你好 我是拉布拉多警长
anywhere please come help us
请你来救救我们
don't worry kids
来帮我们别担心孩子
不要担心孩子
don't worry kids
we'll be right there
别担心孩子,我们马上就到
我们马上就到
we'll be right there
we were playing with little rabbit here
我们在玩小兔子
and suddenly she disappeared
我们在玩小兔子 突然间她失踪了
她忽然间消失,
and suddenly she disappeared
don't worry we'll find little rabbit
别担心 我们会找到小兔子的
right there's no case that I can't solve
别担心,我们会找到小兔子的 没有我办不到的案子
我无法破案
right there's no case that I can't solve
the footprints are only on the manhole
脚印只贴在坑洞上
covers hey kids what game were you
脚脚印只印在坑洞盖上 孩子们 你们玩什么游戏
嘿孩子,你玩什么游戏?
covers hey kids what game were you
playing just now
嘿孩子,你刚才玩什么游戏?
刚才在玩
playing just now
thank you so much fun
谢谢大家,好好玩
stop jumping on manhole covers can be
停止跳跳在 坑洞盖可能
very dangerous watch out
停止跳 跳在坑洞盖 可能非常危险 注意了
Dolby
多尔比
look
外观
at this
此时
ah it's little rabbit's ribbon don't get
这是小兔子的丝带
啊,这是小兔子的丝带 没有得到
ah it's little rabbit's ribbon don't get
close to the manhole I'm going down to
啊,这是小兔子的丝带 不要靠近我要去的坑洞
靠近坑洞的附近,我要去
close to the manhole I'm going down to
help officer Dobby find little rabbit
我要下去帮多比警官找到小兔子
it stinks down here
臭臭臭臭的这下面
this way's blocked
臭气臭气臭的下面 这边堵住了
little rabbit would have gone this way
小兔子会走这条路
did somebody help me please
有人帮我,拜托了
the tunnel splits here which way should
这里的隧道裂开,哪条路应该走哪条路
we go let me listen
这里的隧道裂开 我们该往哪条路走 让我听
我们一起去,让我听
we go let me listen
oh
让我们去,让我听哦
that way
以这种方式
go away go away
离开 离开 离开 离开 离开 离开 离开 离开 离开 离开 离开 离开 离开 离开 离开 离开 离开 离开 离开
don't worry little rabbit we'll get you
别担心小兔子,我们会抓到你的
out of here
别担心小兔子 我们会带你离开这里的
oh no the Wastewater is coming this way
哦,没有废水 来了这条路
Adobe lose those boards
Adobe 失去那些董事会
what's up
这是怎么回事
kids remember never jump on manhole
孩子们记得 永远不要跳到坑洞里
covers again it can be very dangerous
孩子们记得 永远不要再跳在坑洞盖上 可能非常危险
safety talk
安全安全谈话
kids don't step on manhole covers on the
孩子们不要踩在洞口盖上
street and keep away from them when you
孩子们不要踩在街上 街上的坑洞盖上 离他们远一点
你们应当在街上避开他们,当你们在街上和街上与众人交接的时候,
street and keep away from them when you
want you might fall down and get hurt if
当你想要时,你远离街道,而远离街道,你可能会摔倒,而受到伤害,如果
想要你可能摔倒 并受到伤害,如果
want you might fall down and get hurt if
you step on a broken or worn manhole
如果你踩到一个破破破或破旧的坑洞 可能摔倒受伤
踏在破烂或破烂的坑洞上,
you step on a broken or worn manhole
cover also the complicated sewer pipes
踏上破破破或破旧的坑坑盖 以及复杂的下水道管道
还要覆盖复杂的下水道管道
cover also the complicated sewer pipes
harmful gases waste water cockroaches
还包括复杂的下水道管道,有害气体,有害气体,废水,蟑螂
有害有害气体 废水 蟑螂
harmful gases waste water cockroaches
and mice under the manhole cover will
井盖下的蟑螂和小鼠
洞口盖下的小老鼠
and mice under the manhole cover will
make it hard for you to climb back out
老鼠在坑洞盖下 会让你很难爬出来
让你很难爬回来
make it hard for you to climb back out
woof
让你很难爬回来
the biting monster
被咬的怪物
whoa such a pretty mushroom it must be
哇 这么漂亮的蘑菇 一定是
so yummy oh come on Little Beaver time
哇,这么漂亮的蘑菇 一定很美味哦,来吧 小海狸时间
好好吃哦 来吧 小海狸时间
so yummy oh come on Little Beaver time
to eat coming
好好吃哦 来吧 小海狸吃饭时间到了
so yummy
好吃,好吃,好吃,好吃
I want more mushrooms
我要更多蘑菇
and he was so scary
他是如此吓吓人
ah he bit you really hard something's
他是如此可怕啊 他咬你 真的硬的东西
他咬你,真的很难的东西
ah he bit you really hard something's
wrong Toby we need to find Little Beaver
托比 我们需要找到小海狸
托比错了 我们需要找到小海狸
wrong Toby we need to find Little Beaver
now
托比错了 我们需要找到小海狸
okay
还好
with this cushion my bottom will be safe
有了这个垫子,我的底部就安全了
huh
有了这个垫子,我的屁股就安全了
中、英、法、俄、西
huh
where did he go huh
他去了哪里? 去了哪里?
in the bushes let's go
在灌木丛中,我们走吧
isn't that Little Beaver Little Beaver
不是那个小海狸小海狸吗?
something's wrong with him hey Little
是不是小海狸小海狸 他有什么不对劲?
他有什么不对劲吗? 嘿,小
something's wrong with him hey Little
Beaver
小海狸,小海狸,他有点不对劲
Hey Little Beaver
嘿 小海狸 小海狸 小海狸
why me again
为什么又是我
watch out
当心
oh
哦,当心哦
哦
oh
yeah
耶 耶,耶
zombie let's climb up a tree now
僵尸,我们爬树上去吧
oh
哦
no
无 无
mushroom
蘑菇蘑菇
mushroom why is he calling a butterfly a
为什么他叫蝴蝶A
mushroom
蘑菇 为什么他叫蝴蝶蘑菇
what's that
这是什么
can't be
那不可能是什么东西
不可能
can't be
these are little beavers teeth marks I
这些是小海狸牙印
know what's going on little Beaver was
这些是小海狸牙印 我知道小海狸是怎么回事
知道发生了什么事 小海狸是
know what's going on little Beaver was
poisoned by the mushroom that's why he's
小海狸被蘑菇毒害 所以他才...
被蘑菇毒害 所以他
poisoned by the mushroom that's why he's
acting weird
被蘑菇毒害 所以他表现怪怪的
表现怪异
acting weird
poisoned
装作怪怪怪的毒中毒
毒 毒 毒 毒
poisoned
so we look like two big mushrooms to him
被毒毒毒死了 所以我们看起来像两个大蘑菇
所以我们看起来像两个大蘑菇
so we look like two big mushrooms to him
we need to send him to the hospital
所以我们看起来像两个大蘑菇 对他来说,我们需要送他去医院
我们需要送他去医院
we need to send him to the hospital
right now
我们需要马上送他去医院
现在
right now
mushrooms
蘑菇
get back Little Beaver
带回小海狸
get back here get back
回来,回来,回来
oh mushrooms mushrooms he really thinks
回来,回来,哦,蘑菇 蘑菇,他真的认为
哦,蘑菇蘑菇 他真的认为
oh mushrooms mushrooms he really thinks
we're mushrooms let's keep it up
蘑菇蘑菇 他真的认为我们是蘑菇 让我们继续
no no this way this way
这边走,这边走,这边走,这边走
mushrooms mushrooms yes this way this
不,不,这样,这样,这样,这样,这样,这样,这样,这样,是的,这样,这样,这样,是的,这样,这样,这样,这样,是的,这样,这样,这样,这样,是的,这样,这样,这样,这样,是的,这样,这样,这样,这样,这样,这样,是的,这样,这样,这样,这样,这样,这样
蘑菇蘑菇 这边请
mushrooms mushrooms yes this way this
way
蘑菇蘑菇 这边请
方形
way
hurry to the hospital
快点去医院吧
Sheriff Labrador safety talk
拉布拉多警长安全谈话
kids you should beware of mushrooms in
孩子,你应该小心 蘑菇在
the wild they may look colorful and
孩子们,你应该小心野外的蘑菇 他们可能看起来多彩多彩,
野外的野野野,他们或许看起来丰富多彩,
the wild they may look colorful and
pretty but they're very dangerous
野外的野外 可能看起来多姿多彩 漂亮 但他们非常危险
很漂亮,但很危险
pretty but they're very dangerous
because most of them are poisonous never
漂亮,但非常危险 因为他们大多是毒的
因为他们大半是有毒的
because most of them are poisonous never
pick or eat them remember what we
因为他们大部分都是有毒的 永远不摘不吃 永远不吃不摘不摘 记住我们
摘取或食食它们 记住我们
pick or eat them remember what we
learned today
记住我们今天学到的东西
今天学到的今天
learned today
baby swan got lost
婴儿天鹅迷路了
oh Mommy Mommy
婴儿天鹅迷路了哦 妈妈妈妈妈妈
hey little kid are you all right
嘿,小家伙,你没事吧?
don't cry kids we'll help you find your
别哭孩子 我们会帮你找到你的
mommy don't worry there's no case that I
不要哭孩子,我们会帮你找到你的妈妈 不要担心没有我的案子
妈妈别担心没有我的案子
mommy don't worry there's no case that I
can't solve
妈妈不用担心,没有案子我办不了
kid what's your name
孩子,你叫什么名字?
my name is gray
孩子,你叫什么名字 我叫灰色
我的名字是灰色的
my name is gray
and your mommy's name mommy
我的名字是灰灰的 你妈妈的名字是妈妈的妈妈
um I mean what's your mommy's name
我的意思是你妈妈叫什么名字
um it's just Mommy
嗯,只是妈妈
foreign
嗯,只是妈妈外出
外国
foreign
well do you know your mommy's phone
外国好,你知道你妈妈的电话吗?
你知道你妈妈的电话吗?
well do you know your mommy's phone
number maybe
你知道你妈妈的电话号码吗?
hello hello
你好 你好 你好 你好 你好 你好 你好 你好 你好 你好 你好 你好 你好 你好 你好 你好 你好
are you Grace Mommy
你是格蕾丝妈妈
what
你是格蕾丝妈妈什么
什么什么是
what
what gray what
什么灰色什么
Gray
灰色
has my gray skirt arrived no
我的灰色裙子来不来?
no it's nothing I'm sorry hey gray are
我的灰裙子来了,对不起,嘿嘿,灰色的
不,没什么,对不起,嘿,灰色的
no it's nothing I'm sorry hey gray are
you sure it's 77733
不,没什么,对不起,嘿,灰色 你确定是77733吗?
你确定是777733号吗?
you sure it's 77733
uh I don't remember then do you know
你确定是77733号吗? 我不记得了,你知不知道?
我不记得了,你知不知道
uh I don't remember then do you know
your address
嗯,我不记得了 那你知道你的地址吗?
您的地址地址
your address
um no I just know there's a big pond by
不,我只是知道有一个大池塘
嗯,不,我只是知道 有一个大池塘
um no I just know there's a big pond by
my house
嗯,不,我只是知道有一个大池塘 在我家旁边
我的房子,我的房子
my house
a pond the wild goose family live by the
我的房子 池塘 野鹅家庭 生活在
一个池塘野鹅家庭 生活在
a pond the wild goose family live by the
pond great let's go to their house
一只野鹅家的池塘 住在池塘边的野鹅家 我们到他们家去
thank you
感谢您,感谢您
how is it
或妓
Sheriff Labrador can I help you Mr wild
拉布拉多警长 有什么我能帮你的吗 野人先生
goose are all of your children home
拉布拉多警长,我能帮你吗? 野鹅先生都是你的孩子
你所有的孩子都在家吗?
goose are all of your children home
right now I have cars they're all at
鹅是所有你的孩子 回家现在,我现在有汽车,他们都在
现在我有汽车,他们都在
right now I have cars they're all at
home with me everyone gather up
我现在有车,他们都在家,大家集合起来
I have only six children why are there
我只有六个孩子 为什么在那里
seven now
我只有六个孩子 为什么现在有七个孩子
现在 7 个
seven now
oh
7号,现在哦
哦
oh
where where's Gray
哦,哪里的灰色
everyone
每个人,每 人, 每 人, 每 人, 每 人, 每 人, 每 人
wait
等待等待
I got you Gray
等待,我得到了你灰色
I love Mama ice cream oh great do you
我爱妈妈冰淇淇淋 哦,你真好
and your mommy often come here to buy
我爱妈妈冰淇淇淋 哦,太棒了 你和你妈妈经常来这里买冰淇淋吗?
你妈妈经常来这里买
and your mommy often come here to buy
MooMoo ice cream
你妈妈经常来买薄荷冰淇淋
then let's go and ask
那我们就去问吧
may I help you do you know gray here
那么我们走吧,请问 我能帮你吗? 你知道这里灰色的吗?
我可以帮你吗? 你知道这里灰色吗?
may I help you do you know gray here
gray what are you doing here your mommy
我可以帮你吗? 你知道这里灰灰灰的吗? 你在这里做什么? 你妈妈?
灰灰的你在这里做什么 你的妈妈
gray what are you doing here your mommy
was looking for you
灰灰的你在这里做什么 你妈妈找你
找你来找你
was looking for you
where did she go that way
她从那条路往哪去了?
huh
中、英、法、俄、西
a swan so gray is a little swan
灰色是小天鹅
一只天鹅,灰色是一只小天鹅
a swan so gray is a little swan
mommy is missing
妈妈失踪了
she's over there
妈妈失踪了 妈妈在那边
她就在那边
she's over there
where's my child oh
她就在那边 我的孩子在哪啊
哪里是我的孩子啊哦
where's my child oh
I'm coming through sorry excuse me
哪里是我的孩子 哦,我正要通过 对不起,对不起,对不起
借过,对不起,对不起
I'm coming through sorry excuse me
we can't catch up with her what do we do
对不起,对不起,我们追不上她 我们该怎么办?
oh I have an idea again
哦,我又想到一个主意
Miss Swan miss swalla the sheriff
Swan小姐错过了警长的斯瓦拉
Labrador
斯瓦小姐错过了拉布拉多警长的斯瓦拉
拉布拉多
Labrador
finally look over there
拉布拉多终于看那边了
终于看那边了
finally look over there
I'm so worried about you
我好担心你
Sheriff Labradors safety talk
拉布拉多警长安全谈话
kids
儿 童 儿 童
when you go out with your parents you
当你和父母约会的时候
should always stay close to them and if
当你与父母交往时,你应该始终与父母保持密切的亲近,如果
应始终紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧紧
should always stay close to them and if
you lose them stay where you are and
永远跟紧他们 如果你失去他们 留在原地别动
你失去他们 留在原地别动
you lose them stay where you are and
wait for them or ask a police officer
你失去他们,你留在原地,等待他们,或问警察
等候他们或问警察
wait for them or ask a police officer
for help also make sure to memorize your
等他们等他们,或请警察帮忙 还要记住
帮助也确保记住你
for help also make sure to memorize your
parents phone numbers and your home
还要记住你父母的电话号码和你的家
父母电话号码和你的家
parents phone numbers and your home
address it will help police officers
家长电话号码和你的住家地址 将会帮助警官
将帮助警官
address it will help police officers
find your parents please keep these in
帮助警察发现你的父母 请把这些留在
找到父母,请收好
find your parents please keep these in
mind
父母请记住这些
脑心心
mind
dangerous elevator
危险危险电梯
yeah
let's go
我们走
an elevator I have an idea
电梯,我有个主意
my goodness such a naughty boy
电梯,我有一个想法 我的善良,这样一个淘气的男孩
wait
等待等待
move aside to the top floor
移动到顶楼
take the stairs
走楼梯
keep going
继续前进
why is the door opening whoa he's over
为什么门开着,哇,他结束了
there
为什么开门啊,哇啊,他在那边呢
what do you think you are doing don't
你以为你在做什么? 不要
you think it's fun
你以为自己在做什么 你不觉得很好玩吗?
don't even think about it
想都别想
and stop doing it oh finally
并停止做它 哦终于
okay
并停止做它哦 终于可以了
还好
okay
what a day I better not see you again
多么好的日子 我最好不要再见到你了
在那日,我多半不能再见到你,
what a day I better not see you again
bye-bye I need to run huh
多么美好的一天 我最好不要再见到你了 再见 我要跑啊
再见,我需要跑
bye-bye I need to run huh
that's it
拜拜,我要跑,就这样
it's too high
太高了
hurry we're almost there
快点,我们快到了
you again I'm gonna teach you a lesson
再来一次,我教你一课
I need to get out of here open open now
我现在要出去开门了
huh
我要离开这里,现在开门
中、英、法、俄、西
huh
oh
哦
my God
哦,我的上帝,哦,我的上帝
what's going on
发生什么事了
it's over there hurry
发生什么事了? 那边,快点
my treasure my treasure hey whoa
我的宝藏 我的宝藏啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊
stop right there
我的宝藏 我的宝藏 嘿,哇,站住,站住
nobody can run away from me
没有人能逃离我
oh no someone's in there let's go
哦,没有有人在里面,我们走吧
don't worry you're safe now
别担心,你现在安全了
haters again
又是仇恨者
Sheriff Labrador safety talk
拉布拉多警长安全谈话
kids you should follow the safety rules
儿童应当遵守安全规定。
when you take an elevator always ride
儿童在乘电梯时应该遵守安全规则
当你乘坐电梯时 总是坐电梯
when you take an elevator always ride
the elevator with your parents
当你坐电梯时 总是和父母一起坐电梯
和父母一起乘电梯
the elevator with your parents
and never play with the buttons jumping
和父母一起坐电梯 永远不要玩按钮跳
并且永远不玩 与按钮跳动
and never play with the buttons jumping
or playing around is dangerous too and
永远不玩 按钮跳动或玩耍 也是危险的了,
或玩耍也是危险的,
or playing around is dangerous too and
that might cause an accident
或玩耍也是很危险的 可能会引发意外
可能造成意外事故的
that might cause an accident
please remember that
可能造成意外的事故 请记住
请记住,请记住
please remember that
what
请记住,请记住
什么什么是
what
foreign
何为外国
本字幕由AI大模型生成